<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<start>
  <message id="B1" name="B1">
    <say>try to answer the question.</say>
  </message>
  <message id="B2" name="B2">
    <say>, if you are having trouble with the passage, feel free to read along with the audio.</say>
  </message>
  <message id="B3" name="B3">
    <say>I don't think that's it.</say>
  </message>
  <message id="B4" name="B4">
    <say>I don't think that was the right answer.</say>
  </message>
  <message id="B5" name="B5">
    <say>Oops looks like wasn't quite right. </say>
  </message>
  <message id="B6" name="B6">
    <say>Good! You got it right!</say>
  </message>
  <message id="B7" name="B7">
    <say>Super! You got it!</say>
  </message>
  <message id="B8" name="B8">
    <say>Great job! You answered right!</say>
  </message>
  <message id="B9" name="B9">
    <say>You answered correctly! Awesome job!</say>
  </message>
  <message id="B10" name="B10">
    <say>Amazing, you're doing great!</say>
  </message>
  <message id="B11" name="B11">
    <say>Magnificent!</say>
  </message>
  <message id="B12" name="B12">
    <say>Exactly, you nailed it!</say>
  </message>
  <message id="B13" name="B13">
    <say>, Wow, that's it!</say>
  </message>
  <message id="B14" name="B14">
    <say>you really helped me today! Thank you so much! I hope I can get the job!</say>
  </message>
  <message id="B15" name="B15">
    <say>Hi Cristina! I'm great. Now that I have a new place to live and a new credit card. I think I am ready to look for a new job!</say>
  </message>
  <message id="B16" name="B16">
    <say>I just think I need some help filling out the application online. I'm not so good with computers.</say>
  </message>
  <message id="B17" name="B17">
    <say>That sounds perfect Cristina!</say>
  </message>
  <message id="B18" name="B18">
    <say>can you help with a few problem areas?</say>
  </message>
  <message id="B19" name="B19">
    <say>Let's see if we can figure this out together</say>
  </message>
  <message id="B20" name="B20">
    <say>. When filling out an application, what information should you be prepared to give an employer? I think all of this information is important. Which do you think is best?</say>
  </message>
  <message id="B21" name="B21">
    <say>Got it Cristina! This is really helping me to better understand.</say>
  </message>
  <message id="B22" name="B22">
    <say>Here's the next question</say>
  </message>
  <message id="B23" name="B23">
    <say>. Why is important to be completely honest when filling out an application? I think it is important to always be honest but if I had to choose I think it just shows you have bad morals.</say>
  </message>
  <message id="B24" name="B24">
    <say>Oh, that is important information to remember. </say>
  </message>
  <message id="B25" name="B25">
    <say>Which position do you think I should apply for? Check my resume if you need</say>
  </message>
  <message id="B26" name="B26">
    <say>That is a great choice! I enjoy serving customers and have the experience. </say>
  </message>
  <message id="B27" name="B27">
    <say>I'm not sure which skills best show that I can talk to customers. What would you choose? Just type your answer below. The choices are underlined in this job posting I found.</say>
  </message>
  <message id="B28" name="B28">
    <say>That is important to speaking with customers. I didn't even consider it. Awesome!</say>
  </message>
  <message id="B29" name="B29">
    <say>and Cristina I told you I was not good with computers! I can't believe I selected the wrong button.</say>
  </message>
  <message id="B30" name="B30">
    <say>Oops! I did graduate and what a silly mistake! I am glad we caught it before I turned in my application. </say>
  </message>
  <message id="B31" name="B31">
    <say>Alright Cristina, I think I'm getting this!</say>
  </message>
  <message id="B32" name="B32">
    <say>Which reference do you think is best for applying to Eastside Grill? You can type your answer into the boxes with the red star next them.</say>
  </message>
  <message id="B33" name="B33">
    <say>Well, I am pretty good at washing cars. </say>
  </message>
</start>