<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<start>
  <message id="A1" name="A1">
    <say>Jordan and</say>
  </message>
  <message id="A2" name="A2">
    <say>, unfortunately neither of you are correct.</say>
  </message>
  <message id="A3" name="A3">
    <say>No sorry Jordan and</say>
  </message>
  <message id="A4" name="A4">
    <say>, neither of you are correct.</say>
  </message>
  <message id="A5" name="A5">
    <say>Choose an answer please!</say>
  </message>
  <message id="A6" name="A6">
    <say>, you are really getting this!</say>
  </message>
  <message id="A7" name="A7">
    <say>, you are correct! Great job!</say>
  </message>
  <message id="A8" name="A8">
    <say>Excellent</say>
  </message>
  <message id="A9" name="A9">
    <say>, can you please click on the correct answer choice?</say>
  </message>
  <message id="A10" name="A10">
    <say>That is not right.</say>
  </message>
  <message id="A11" name="A11">
    <say>Please try again.</say>
  </message>
  <message id="A12" name="A12">
    <say>Great Jordan and</say>
  </message>
  <message id="A13" name="A13">
    <say>Jordan and</say>
  </message>
  <message id="A14" name="A14">
    <say>, you are both correct!</say>
  </message>
  <message id="A15" name="A15">
    <say>Excellent the both of you!</say>
  </message>
  <message id="A16" name="A16">
    <say>Jordan and</say>
  </message>
  <message id="A17" name="A17">
    <say>, you are both going to become great writers one day!</say>
  </message>
  <message id="A18" name="A18">
    <say>Both of your answers are correct!</say>
  </message>
  <message id="A19" name="A19">
    <say>Jordan, can you answer this question?</say>
  </message>
  <message id="A20" name="A20">
    <say>, can you please choose one and drag it to the blank?</say>
  </message>
  <message id="A21" name="A21">
    <say>Jordan, you are correct!</say>
  </message>
  <message id="A22" name="A22">
    <say>Jordan, you are right on this one!</say>
  </message>
  <message id="A23" name="A23">
    <say>Jordan, your answer is correct!</say>
  </message>
  <message id="A24" name="A24">
    <say>What an exciting story.  You used your knowledge of how narrative texts are arranged to create your own story!  I hope you enjoyed this activity.</say>
  </message>
  <message id="A25" name="A25">
    <say>Hi Jordan and</say>
  </message>
  <message id="A26" name="A26">
    <say>, it's Cristina once again to tell you about the activities.</say>
  </message>
  <message id="A27" name="A27">
    <say>In this activity, you will answer questions about basic plot structure in narrative texts. After each question you will be given a piece of a story. You can fill in the blanks of the story to create your own version.</say>
  </message>
  <message id="A28" name="A28">
    <say>Great! In order to fill in the blanks, you will click one of the button options and drag that option to a blank area in the sentence. When the line under the blank turns green,  you will know that your answer can be dropped into the sentence.</say>
  </message>
  <message id="A29" name="A29">
    <say>Let's start developing the beginning of your story. What is one element that needs to be introduced in the beginning of your story? Please click on either A, B, or C.</say>
  </message>
  <message id="A30" name="A30">
    <say>The correct answer is A. whenever you tell a story, you need to introduce the characters.  </say>
  </message>
  <message id="A31" name="A31">
    <say>Now that you know how to begin your story, you can start by choosing two characters from the list below and drag them to the blanks. The two characters you choose will be your story's main characters</say>
  </message>
  <message id="A32" name="A32">
    <say>Good selection Jordan and</say>
  </message>
  <message id="A33" name="A33">
    <say>, these two will be your story's main characters. Now let's continue building your story!</say>
  </message>
  <message id="A34" name="A34">
    <say>Choose an answer</say>
  </message>
  <message id="A35" name="A35">
    <say>Jordan and</say>
  </message>
  <message id="A36" name="A36">
    <say>, what element describes when and where a story takes place? This element may change. Please click on either A, B, or C next to the correct answer choice. Please click on either A, B, or C.</say>
  </message>
  <message id="A37" name="A37">
    <say>The correct answer is B. You need to establish the setting early on in the story, but the setting may change a lot as the story progresses. </say>
  </message>
  <message id="A38" name="A38">
    <say>Now that you know that you need to establish the setting, Jordan and</say>
  </message>
  <message id="A39" name="A39">
    <say>, please choose a setting with a time and a place from the list below and drag them to the blanks.</say>
  </message>
  <message id="A40" name="A40">
    <say>Nice settings Jordan and</say>
  </message>
  <message id="A41" name="A41">
    <say>, you two are being very creative!</say>
  </message>
  <message id="A42" name="A42">
    <say>Now that you two have chosen a setting, let's continue. Jordan and</say>
  </message>
  <message id="A43" name="A43">
    <say>, what is the element of a story that creates conflict for the characters? Please click on either A, B, or C.</say>
  </message>
  <message id="A44" name="A44">
    <say>The correct answer is A. In the beginning of the story, there typically is a problem.</say>
  </message>
  <message id="A45" name="A45">
    <say>Now that you know that you must introduce a problem at the beginning of the story,</say>
  </message>
  <message id="A46" name="A46">
    <say>, please choose a problem from the list below and drag it to the blank.</say>
  </message>
  <message id="A47" name="A47">
    <say>Interesting problem!  Let's go on.</say>
  </message>
  <message id="A48" name="A48">
    <say>There has been a lot of events so far in the story! Jordan and</say>
  </message>
  <message id="A49" name="A49">
    <say>,  what happens at the most important point of the story? Please click on either A, B, or C.</say>
  </message>
  <message id="A50" name="A50">
    <say>The correct answer is C. when something happens that complicates the problem it leads up to a major event. </say>
  </message>
  <message id="A51" name="A51">
    <say>Now, we know that you must have a major event follow the problem,</say>
  </message>
  <message id="A52" name="A52">
    <say>, let's read the middle of the story, choose a major event from the list below and drag it to the blank.</say>
  </message>
  <message id="A53" name="A53">
    <say>Great choice of major event</say>
  </message>
  <message id="A54" name="A54">
    <say>!  Let's move on to the ending of your story.</say>
  </message>
  <message id="A55" name="A55">
    <say>Jordan and</say>
  </message>
  <message id="A56" name="A56">
    <say>, can you tell me what happens at the end of a story? Please click on either A, B, or C.</say>
  </message>
  <message id="A57" name="A57">
    <say>The correct answer is A, the ending of the story is where the problem is finally solved.</say>
  </message>
  <message id="A58" name="A58">
    <say>Now that you know what the ending of a story is,</say>
  </message>
  <message id="A59" name="A59">
    <say>, we need an ending for your story. Please select an ending and drag it to the blank.</say>
  </message>
  <message id="A60" name="A60">
    <say>Great ending and a good way to resolve the story's problem!</say>
  </message>
  <message id="A61" name="A61">
    <say>You know what I think will make this story even better</say>
  </message>
  <message id="A62" name="A62">
    <say>and Jordan? A title!</say>
  </message>
  <message id="A63" name="A63">
    <say>, why don't you give the story a title?</say>
  </message>
  <message id="A64" name="A64">
    <say>Before we look at your finished story, let's come up with a title for it!</say>
  </message>
</start>