<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<start>
  <message id="A1" name="A1">
    <say>, sorry! that wasn't what I was looking for.</say>
  </message>
  <message id="A2" name="A2">
    <say>, Well, not quite, That wasn't the right choice.</say>
  </message>
  <message id="A3" name="A3">
    <say>, Whoops! Looks like you picked the wrong answer.</say>
  </message>
  <message id="A4" name="A4">
    <say>Better luck next time! That wasn't the best answer.</say>
  </message>
  <message id="A5" name="A5">
    <say>Great job!</say>
  </message>
  <message id="A6" name="A6">
    <say>, Good! That is right.</say>
  </message>
  <message id="A7" name="A7">
    <say>You are correct!</say>
  </message>
  <message id="A8" name="A8">
    <say>, Perfect! You got it right!</say>
  </message>
  <message id="A9" name="A9">
    <say>great! You answered correctly.</say>
  </message>
  <message id="A10" name="A10">
    <say>. You got it right!</say>
  </message>
  <message id="A11" name="A11">
    <say>, Exactly! You are right!</say>
  </message>
  <message id="A12" name="A12">
    <say>, Amazing!</say>
  </message>
  <message id="A13" name="A13">
    <say>, Awesome job! You answered correctly!</say>
  </message>
  <message id="A14" name="A14">
    <say>, Just superb! You're incredible!</say>
  </message>
  <message id="A15" name="A15">
    <say>, Brilliant job! You got it right!</say>
  </message>
  <message id="A16" name="A16">
    <say>, Perfect! Good work.</say>
  </message>
  <message id="A17" name="A17">
    <say>, Well done! You're good!</say>
  </message>
  <message id="A18" name="A18">
    <say>, That's correct! You're doing beautifully!</say>
  </message>
  <message id="A19" name="A19">
    <say>, You rock my socks off! Awesome job getting that one right!</say>
  </message>
  <message id="A20" name="A20">
    <say>, Well, actually, that is not what I was looking for.</say>
  </message>
  <message id="A21" name="A21">
    <say>, Whoops! you are not correct.</say>
  </message>
  <message id="A22" name="A22">
    <say>, Oh sorry, that isn't what I was looking for</say>
  </message>
  <message id="A23" name="A23">
    <say>, Not exactly, good try</say>
  </message>
  <message id="A24" name="A24">
    <say>, Well, that wasn't what I was thinking. Here is the best choice in green</say>
  </message>
  <message id="A25" name="A25">
    <say>try your best and answer the question.</say>
  </message>
  <message id="A26" name="A26">
    <say>Please try it.</say>
  </message>
  <message id="A27" name="A27">
    <say>Please select an answer</say>
  </message>
  <message id="A28" name="A28">
    <say>Ok</say>
  </message>
  <message id="A29" name="A29">
    <say>here is the answer.</say>
  </message>
  <message id="A30" name="A30">
    <say>Jordan, Wonderful! You answered the question correctly.</say>
  </message>
  <message id="A31" name="A31">
    <say>Jordan, You rock! That's right!</say>
  </message>
  <message id="A32" name="A32">
    <say>Jordan, That's right!</say>
  </message>
  <message id="A33" name="A33">
    <say>Jordan, great work! You got it right!</say>
  </message>
  <message id="A34" name="A34">
    <say>Jordan, Awesome work! That's it!</say>
  </message>
  <message id="A35" name="A35">
    <say>, if you are having trouble with the passage, feel free to read along with the audio.</say>
  </message>
  <message id="A36" name="A36">
    <say>If you are having trouble reading the passage, then you can read along with the audio, by pressing the read audio button</say>
  </message>
  <message id="A37" name="A37">
    <say>I hope you two learned some things about online applications today. </say>
  </message>
  <message id="A38" name="A38">
    <say>Good luck Jordan! Goodbye</say>
  </message>
  <message id="A39" name="A39">
    <say>Welcome back</say>
  </message>
  <message id="A40" name="A40">
    <say>and Jordan! Hope everyone is doing well.</say>
  </message>
  <message id="A41" name="A41">
    <say>Jordan, that's great! Well, you already have a resume. So maybe</say>
  </message>
  <message id="A42" name="A42">
    <say>and I can help!</say>
  </message>
  <message id="A43" name="A43">
    <say>let's see if we can help Jordan fill out his application today! Please help Jordan with some of his questions. I will be here along the way to help.</say>
  </message>
  <message id="A44" name="A44">
    <say>Experience, education, and contact information is the best answer. Personal information such as religious affiliation should not be given. And credit history is often not a requirement by employers. </say>
  </message>
  <message id="A45" name="A45">
    <say>Please select an answer. </say>
  </message>
  <message id="A46" name="A46">
    <say>Dishonesty could result in not being hired. You should always provide correct and up to date information. Any mistakes could cost you the job.</say>
  </message>
  <message id="A47" name="A47">
    <say>Please select an answer choice. </say>
  </message>
  <message id="A48" name="A48">
    <say>Server is a good choice based on Jordan's information. However, he could always apply for any open position. </say>
  </message>
  <message id="A49" name="A49">
    <say>Please select an answer. </say>
  </message>
  <message id="A50" name="A50">
    <say>Communication skills would be the best answer. Communication is the sharing of information. What better way to share that by talking. However, a positive attitude might help too!</say>
  </message>
  <message id="A51" name="A51">
    <say>That's not quite what I was looking for. A better answer could be something like communication skills. </say>
  </message>
  <message id="A52" name="A52">
    <say>The best answer would be communication skills or even just having a positive attitude.</say>
  </message>
  <message id="A53" name="A53">
    <say>Please type an answer.</say>
  </message>
  <message id="A54" name="A54">
    <say>communication</say>
  </message>
  <message id="A55" name="A55">
    <say>well-organized</say>
  </message>
  <message id="A56" name="A56">
    <say>Remember, we are look for the kind of job Jordan would like to get. Type the best answer below.</say>
  </message>
  <message id="A57" name="A57">
    <say>That is a great answer! I think you are on the right track.</say>
  </message>
  <message id="A58" name="A58">
    <say>Oh that isn't quite what I was looking for. The best answer would be something like communication skills.</say>
  </message>
  <message id="A59" name="A59">
    <say>Let's get started on a few things Jordan had trouble with on his application. Here's the next question. Has Jordan ever been employed by Eastside Grill restaurants before? Jordan has selected the box for no. Let's refer to Jordan's resume to double check his answers for this section. Please click the button at the bottom for yes or no to respond.</say>
  </message>
  <message id="A60" name="A60">
    <say>The correct answer is yes. We can find this information on Jordan's resume. He has worked for this company before in a different city. Always double check your selections because remember dishonesty can result in not getting the job. </say>
  </message>
  <message id="A61" name="A61">
    <say>Please select an answer.</say>
  </message>
  <message id="A62" name="A62">
    <say>Jordan has marked that he did not graduate from high school? According to his resume, is this information correct? Please select yes or no at the bottom to submit your answer.</say>
  </message>
  <message id="A63" name="A63">
    <say>Jordan did graduate from high school. The correct answer is yes. Again, it is important to make sure that you click the correct buttons when filling out a resume or you run the risk of not being hired. </say>
  </message>
  <message id="A64" name="A64">
    <say>Please select an answer.</say>
  </message>
  <message id="A65" name="A65">
    <say>Click the task that is the most related to the open serving position.</say>
  </message>
  <message id="A66" name="A66">
    <say>Seated and obtained orders is the best answer. Because seating and taking orders is experience that can be used in many different settings. Every restaurant may not be the same and some of the tasks listed may not apply to serving anywhere rather than just on place.  </say>
  </message>
  <message id="A67" name="A67">
    <say>Please select an answer. </say>
  </message>
  <message id="A68" name="A68">
    <say>Chelsea Jones is a good answer!</say>
  </message>
  <message id="A69" name="A69">
    <say>Not quite what I was looking for. Though</say>
  </message>
  <message id="A70" name="A70">
    <say>Well, we now know that Jordan has worked for Eastside Grill before. He may want to use his former manager from the restaurant as a reference. She may be able to offer information to his potential new employer that could be helpful for getting the job. </say>
  </message>
  <message id="A71" name="A71">
    <say>Please select an answer. </say>
  </message>
  <message id="A72" name="A72">
    <say>Chelsea Jones is a good answer because she is a former manager of Jordan's. She also works for the same brand of restaurants as Jordan is applying for. </say>
  </message>
  <message id="A73" name="A73">
    <say>bob</say>
  </message>
  <message id="A74" name="A74">
    <say>Think about what kind of washing Jordan could do in a restaurant. What do you think the best answer might be?</say>
  </message>
  <message id="A75" name="A75">
    <say>Not a bad answer but I think there might be another person who is better on this list. Try again. </say>
  </message>
  <message id="A76" name="A76">
    <say>bob</say>
  </message>
</start>