  <message id="A1" name="A1">
    <say>Ok</say>
  </message>
  <message id="A2" name="A2">
    <say>here is the answer.</say>
  </message>
  <message id="A3" name="A3">
    <say>, sorry! that wasn't what I was looking for.</say>
  </message>
  <message id="A4" name="A4">
    <say>, Well, not quite, That wasn't the right choice.</say>
  </message>
  <message id="A5" name="A5">
    <say>, Whoops! Looks like you picked the wrong answer.</say>
  </message>
  <message id="A6" name="A6">
    <say>Better luck next time! That wasn't the best answer.</say>
  </message>
  <message id="A7" name="A7">
    <say>Jordan, you didn't pick the correct answer!</say>
  </message>
  <message id="A8" name="A8">
    <say>Jordan, you actually got that question wrong!</say>
  </message>
  <message id="A9" name="A9">
    <say>Jordan, that's not right!</say>
  </message>
  <message id="A10" name="A10">
    <say>Jordan, you gave an incorrect answer.</say>
  </message>
  <message id="A11" name="A11">
    <say>Jordan, you were wrong.</say>
  </message>
  <message id="A12" name="A12">
    <say>Sorry, Jordan, that's not right.</say>
  </message>
  <message id="A13" name="A13">
    <say>, Well, actually, that is not what I was looking for.</say>
  </message>
  <message id="A14" name="A14">
    <say>, Whoops! you are not correct.</say>
  </message>
  <message id="A15" name="A15">
    <say>, Oh sorry, that isn't what I was looking for</say>
  </message>
  <message id="A16" name="A16">
    <say>, Not exactly, good try</say>
  </message>
  <message id="A17" name="A17">
    <say>W </say>
  </message>
  <message id="A18" name="A18">
    <say>Great job!</say>
  </message>
  <message id="A19" name="A19">
    <say>, Good! That is right.</say>
  </message>
  <message id="A20" name="A20">
    <say>You are correct!</say>
  </message>
  <message id="A21" name="A21">
    <say>, Perfect! You got it right!</say>
  </message>
  <message id="A22" name="A22">
    <say>great! You answered correctly.</say>
  </message>
  <message id="A23" name="A23">
    <say>. You got it right!</say>
  </message>
  <message id="A24" name="A24">
    <say>, Exactly! You are right!</say>
  </message>
  <message id="A25" name="A25">
    <say>, Amazing!</say>
  </message>
  <message id="A26" name="A26">
    <say>, Awesome job! You answered correctly!</say>
  </message>
  <message id="A27" name="A27">
    <say>, Just superb! You're incredible!</say>
  </message>
  <message id="A28" name="A28">
    <say>, Brilliant job! You got it right!</say>
  </message>
  <message id="A29" name="A29">
    <say>, Perfect! Good work.</say>
  </message>
  <message id="A30" name="A30">
    <say>, Well done! You're good!</say>
  </message>
  <message id="A31" name="A31">
    <say>, That's correct! You're doing beautifully!</say>
  </message>
  <message id="A32" name="A32">
    <say>, You rock my socks off! Awesome job getting that one right!</say>
  </message>
  <message id="A33" name="A33">
    <say>Thank you for typing! This contains everything that was asked in the question</say>
  </message>
  <message id="A34" name="A34">
    <say>Jordan, Wonderful! You answered the question correctly.</say>
  </message>
  <message id="A35" name="A35">
    <say>Jordan, You rock! That's right!</say>
  </message>
  <message id="A36" name="A36">
    <say>Jordan, That's right!</say>
  </message>
  <message id="A37" name="A37">
    <say>Jordan, great work! You got it right!</say>
  </message>
  <message id="A38" name="A38">
    <say>Jordan, Awesome work! That's it!</say>
  </message>
  <message id="A39" name="A39">
    <say>Oh rats! Sorry you two that wasn't what I was looking for.</say>
  </message>
  <message id="A40" name="A40">
    <say>Uh oh</say>
  </message>
  <message id="A41" name="A41">
    <say>and Jordan! That wasn't the correct answer.</say>
  </message>
  <message id="A42" name="A42">
    <say>Whoops! Neither of you gave me the answer that I was looking for.</say>
  </message>
  <message id="A43" name="A43">
    <say>Sorry you two! That wasn't right. </say>
  </message>
  <message id="A44" name="A44">
    <say>Not quite</say>
  </message>
  <message id="A45" name="A45">
    <say>and Jordan! You both got that one incorrect.</say>
  </message>
  <message id="A46" name="A46">
    <say>try typing something that contains everything that was asked in the question</say>
  </message>
  <message id="A47" name="A47">
    <say>try your best and answer the question.</say>
  </message>
  <message id="A48" name="A48">
    <say>Dynamite!</say>
  </message>
  <message id="A49" name="A49">
    <say>and Jordan you are both correct!</say>
  </message>
  <message id="A50" name="A50">
    <say>Phenomenal work you two! Way to go on getting it right!</say>
  </message>
  <message id="A51" name="A51">
    <say>Great answer you two! Outstanding work!</say>
  </message>
  <message id="A52" name="A52">
    <say>and Jordan that's correct! Smooth move you two!</say>
  </message>
  <message id="A53" name="A53">
    <say>You two rule! That's right!</say>
  </message>
  <message id="A54" name="A54">
    <say>Excellent work! You are both right!</say>
  </message>
  <message id="A55" name="A55">
    <say>, if you are having trouble with the passage, feel free to read along with the audio.</say>
  </message>
  <message id="A56" name="A56">
    <say>If you are having trouble reading the passage, then you can read along with the audio, by pressing the read audio button</say>
  </message>
  <message id="A57" name="A57">
    <say>That is great! I'm excited for Jordan! Being invited to parties of your classmates can be so much fun! Remember that you can reply to a message by clicking on the reply button. This will allow you to respond directly to the sender of the message. The reply all button will send a message to Erica and everyone else in the class. Sometimes you may not want to respond to everyone in class, it depends on what you want to say</say>
  </message>
  <message id="A58" name="A58">
    <say>Great! I'm happy you sent the message to Erica. Whenever you send a message, you will be directed back to your inbox! Or you can be directed back to another message, similar to what was just done. It looks like Jordan has a meeting at 3 o clock today! Let's reed it to see what it's about</say>
  </message>
  <message id="A59" name="A59">
    <say>Hi Jordan and</say>
  </message>
  <message id="A60" name="A60">
    <say>! Welcome back to Seesaw!</say>
  </message>
  <message id="A61" name="A61">
    <say>Well Jordan, we can help you with that! I think</say>
  </message>
  <message id="A62" name="A62">
    <say>can help you answer whatever questions you may have!</say>
  </message>
  <message id="A63" name="A63">
    <say>Great let's get started!</say>
  </message>
  <message id="A64" name="A64">
    <say>Let's take a look at Jordan's account now! Click login whenever you're ready!</say>
  </message>
  <message id="A65" name="A65">
    <say>Great message to Ms. Johnson and Dr. Arthur! It looks like we answered all of the urgent messages in Jordan's inbox. Let's go ahead and sign out! I think we're done for the day.</say>
  </message>
  <message id="A66" name="A66">
    <say>Thank you</say>
  </message>
  <message id="A67" name="A67">
    <say>for helping Jordan type and send emails and navigate through his new account! Jordan has now been signed out of his email account. In order to log back in he must reenter his password in the password box below.</say>
  </message>
  <message id="A68" name="A68">
    <say>Great Jordan! You two have a wonderful day! </say>
  </message>
  <message id="A69" name="A69">
    <say>Great! Now that we have the normal email out of the spam folder we can delete the spam emails! You will notice that your spam folder will constantly be full of messages. It is important that you always empty it out.</say>
  </message>
  <message id="A70" name="A70">
    <say>Let's get started with the message to Jeanine and Dr. Arthur now!</say>
  </message>
  <message id="A71" name="A71">
    <say>great work! You clicked on the login button, many email accounts will have different login styles but they all require you to do the same thing, which is put in your _user_name and password but remember to never share those with anyone</say>
  </message>
  <message id="A72" name="A72">
    <say>Great!</say>
  </message>
  <message id="A73" name="A73">
    <say>and Jordan  there will be all types of emails inside of your inbox. some will be real and some will be spam! People will try to steal your information and take over your account. It is important to be able to tell the difference! It looks like there are 2 spam emails inside of Jordan's inbox already! wow!</say>
  </message>
  <message id="A74" name="A74">
    <say>we're about to find out Jordan! Let's take a look!</say>
  </message>
  <message id="A75" name="A75">
    <say>displayed is what a good subject line would look like! Let's try typing an email for Jordan now!</say>
  </message>
  <message id="A76" name="A76">
    <say>Whoops!It looks like an email was sent to the spam folder by mistake! Sometimes this happens when your email account does not recognize the email address of the sender!</say>
  </message>
  <message id="A77" name="A77">
    <say>Yes, great work!</say>
  </message>
  <message id="A78" name="A78">
    <say>I think it is important to send a friendly message back to thank Jeanine Johnson for sending you a reminder email about your meeting with Dr. Arthur. And confirmation to Dr. Arthur telling him Jordan will be at the meeting.</say>
  </message>
  <message id="A79" name="A79">
    <say>I think it's important for Jordan to know the difference between the folders he has in his email account. Can you click on the inbox folder for me?</say>
  </message>
  <message id="A80" name="A80">
    <say>This is the inbox, It is highlighted green. The inbox holds all of Jordan's current emails.</say>
  </message>
  <message id="A81" name="A81">
    <say>please select the inbox?</say>
  </message>
  <message id="A82" name="A82">
    <say>Note that spam mail looks different from normal emails, they have funny characters and weird sayings, like "click here to claim your new car!"</say>
  </message>
  <message id="A83" name="A83">
    <say>Please select all of the spam mail in the inbox.</say>
  </message>
  <message id="A84" name="A84">
    <say>The email entitled Erica and Rachel's party was sent to the spam folder! Jordan's email account did not recognize the email address from the sender and placed it inside of this folder. This sometimes happens.</say>
  </message>
  <message id="A85" name="A85">
    <say>Please move the email back to the right folder</say>
  </message>
  <message id="A86" name="A86">
    <say>You selected the inbox folder. That was the correct folder.</say>
  </message>
  <message id="A87" name="A87">
    <say>You selected the outbox folder, the correct folder is the inbox folder.</say>
  </message>
  <message id="A88" name="A88">
    <say>You selected the spam folder, the right folder is the inbox folder</say>
  </message>
  <message id="A89" name="A89">
    <say>You selected the trash folder, the folder that should have been picked is the inbox folder</say>
  </message>
  <message id="A90" name="A90">
    <say>To delete messages you always click on the trash bin! The trash bin will delete the emails you selected. When you select emails to delete be sure that you really want to get rid of them because once you click on the trash bin the emails are deleted forever!</say>
  </message>
  <message id="A91" name="A91">
    <say>Please click on a button to delete the spam emails.</say>
  </message>
  <message id="A92" name="A92">
    <say>Jordan's email that landed in the spam folder was not spam at all! Click on the inbox folder and then click on the email from Jordan's friends so he can read it.</say>
  </message>
  <message id="A93" name="A93">
    <say>That is the message from Jordan's friend! Now let's read it!</say>
  </message>
  <message id="A94" name="A94">
    <say>Please click on the email from Jordan's friend.</say>
  </message>
  <message id="A95" name="A95">
    <say>You should click on the reply button! This will allow you to reply only to Erica in the message.</say>
  </message>
  <message id="A96" name="A96">
    <say>Please select an answer. </say>
  </message>
  <message id="A97" name="A97">
    <say>before you send the message for Jordan! Can you type in an appropriate subject line? A subject line should tell the receiver the main reason why you're sending the email. Since this is an email from Jordan telling Erica that he wants to help the subject line should say this.</say>
  </message>
  <message id="A98" name="A98">
    <say>That is a very fitting subject line for our email to Jordan's classmate. Here is another example of a good subject line</say>
  </message>
  <message id="A99" name="A99">
    <say>thanks! displayed here is an example of an appropriate subjectline</say>
  </message>
  <message id="A100" name="A100">
    <say>That is a really good subject line! Thank you for typing!</say>
  </message>
  <message id="A101" name="A101">
    <say>when writing a subjectline, make sure it entails the message you want the receiver to know before they open it. So for example, if I want to send a message to my boss about running late to a meeting I’d make the subjectline “Running late to meeting.” Use this idea to create a subjectline for Erica and Rachel’s party.</say>
  </message>
  <message id="A102" name="A102">
    <say>That is a great answer! I think you are on the right track.</say>
  </message>
  <message id="A103" name="A103">
    <say>can you send an email back to Erica telling her that Jordan would like to help her set up for the party this weekend? Please be sure to write a greeting such as hi Erica and Rachel and a signature such as from Jordan,or  thanks Jordan. It is always important to address the receiver when you first start a message and when you end a message by using a signature. When you are finished please click the send email button.</say>
  </message>
  <message id="A104" name="A104">
    <say>here is an example of a good email to send</say>
  </message>
  <message id="A105" name="A105">
    <say>That was a great message! Displayed here is another example of what a good email could be. It contains all of the appropriate information needed.</say>
  </message>
  <message id="A106" name="A106">
    <say>That is really good email! Thank you for typing!</say>
  </message>
  <message id="A107" name="A107">
    <say>That is not quite the answer I was looking for.</say>
  </message>
  <message id="A108" name="A108">
    <say>when writing an email, create a message that allows the receiver to know the exact purpose of your email. So in this case, telling the receivers that you can help for decorate for their party is a great message to relay.</say>
  </message>
  <message id="A109" name="A109">
    <say>That is a great answer! I think you are on the right track.</say>
  </message>
  <message id="A110" name="A110">
    <say>Oh that isn't quite what I was looking for.</say>
  </message>
  <message id="A111" name="A111">
    <say>Selecting reply all is the best option. There are two people on this current email, Jeanine Johnson and Dr. Arthur.</say>
  </message>
  <message id="A112" name="A112">
    <say>Please select an answer.</say>
  </message>
  <message id="A113" name="A113">
    <say>before you type your message remember to type in an appropriate subjectline. So go ahead and type in a subjectline that says Thank you for the reminder.</say>
  </message>
  <message id="A114" name="A114">
    <say>I really think that is a great subjectline! Displayed is another example of a good subjectline.</say>
  </message>
  <message id="A115" name="A115">
    <say>can you please type a different subjectline in the subjectline bar.</say>
  </message>
  <message id="A116" name="A116">
    <say>That is really good email! Thank you for typing!</say>
  </message>
  <message id="A117" name="A117">
    <say>when writing a subjectline, make sure it encompasses the overall message you’d like to receiver to know. This way, they will have a general idea of the purpose of your message.</say>
  </message>
  <message id="A118" name="A118">
    <say>That is a great answer! I think you are on the right track.</say>
  </message>
  <message id="A119" name="A119">
    <say>Can you please tell Ms. Jeanine that Jordan said thank you for reminding him about his meeting with Dr. Arthur! And can you tell Dr. Arthur that Jordan will be at his office at 3.</say>
  </message>
  <message id="A120" name="A120">
    <say>That is a nice email</say>
  </message>
  <message id="A121" name="A121">
    <say>! thank you for typing it. Displayed is yet another example of good email.</say>
  </message>
  <message id="A122" name="A122">
    <say>try typing a different email that is more fitting.</say>
  </message>
  <message id="A123" name="A123">
    <say>That is a really good email! Thank you for typing!</say>
  </message>
  <message id="A124" name="A124">
    <say>when writing an email to two people, it is important to address them both. Also, be sure to make the purpose of your email clear. Thank Jeanine Johnson for her reminder and let Dr. Arthur know that you will see him during your meeting. So a short and sweet email that says thank you will do just fine.</say>
  </message>
  <message id="A125" name="A125">
    <say>That is a great answer! I think you are on the right track.</say>
  </message>
  <message id="A126" name="A126">
    <say>Oh that isn't quite what I was looking for.</say>
  </message>