  <message id="B1" name="B1">
    <say>try to answer the question.</say>
  </message>
  <message id="B2" name="B2">
    <say>, if you are having trouble with the passage, feel free to read along with the audio.</say>
  </message>
  <message id="B3" name="B3">
    <say>Um...</say>
  </message>
  <message id="B4" name="B4">
    <say>I don't think that's the right answer.</say>
  </message>
  <message id="B5" name="B5">
    <say>Um...</say>
  </message>
  <message id="B6" name="B6">
    <say>I don't think that was the right answer.</say>
  </message>
  <message id="B7" name="B7">
    <say>, that wasn't the right answer.</say>
  </message>
  <message id="B8" name="B8">
    <say>Good! You got it right!</say>
  </message>
  <message id="B9" name="B9">
    <say>Super! You got it!</say>
  </message>
  <message id="B10" name="B10">
    <say>Great job! You answered right!</say>
  </message>
  <message id="B11" name="B11">
    <say>You answered correctly! Awesome job!</say>
  </message>
  <message id="B12" name="B12">
    <say>Amazing, you're doing great!</say>
  </message>
  <message id="B13" name="B13">
    <say>Magnificent!</say>
  </message>
  <message id="B14" name="B14">
    <say>Exactly, you nailed it!</say>
  </message>
  <message id="B15" name="B15">
    <say>, Wow, that's it!</say>
  </message>
  <message id="B16" name="B16">
    <say>Cristina! I am having a dilemma! I have a new email account that I don't know how to use!</say>
  </message>
  <message id="B17" name="B17">
    <say>Oh</say>
  </message>
  <message id="B18" name="B18">
    <say>would you!? That would be great! Okay here it is!</say>
  </message>
  <message id="B19" name="B19">
    <say>Cool!</say>
  </message>
  <message id="B20" name="B20">
    <say>You are such a big help! thank you! Cristina I think I will log back in later on to check my inbox for new emails.</say>
  </message>
  <message id="B21" name="B21">
    <say>Thanks</say>
  </message>
  <message id="B22" name="B22">
    <say>and Cristina for all of your help today! See you later.</say>
  </message>
  <message id="B23" name="B23">
    <say>I'm excited to see what message my friend  sent to me!</say>
  </message>
  <message id="B24" name="B24">
    <say>Thanks</say>
  </message>
  <message id="B25" name="B25">
    <say>! All of the spam emails are in the spam folder!</say>
  </message>
  <message id="B26" name="B26">
    <say>thanks for all of your help with emptying the spam folder!</say>
  </message>
  <message id="B27" name="B27">
    <say>since Cristina is talking about spam mail,  I've clicked two emails that I believe to be spam. Do you think these two emails are spam? Yes or No?</say>
  </message>
  <message id="B28" name="B28">
    <say>there is an email in the spam folder from one of my friends! I've already clicked the email and I need to move it back to the inbox folder. Can you move this email to the inbox folder by clicking on the folder for me?</say>
  </message>
  <message id="B29" name="B29">
    <say>which button do I press to get rid of the spam messages? The spam mail has been clicked, all you have to do is click on the correct button.</say>
  </message>
  <message id="B30" name="B30">
    <say>Look! this is cool! I got invited to a party! I'd like to help Erica set up her party this weekend! Can you send her a message for me and tell her that? Which button would I press to reply to her to begin typing?</say>
  </message>
  <message id="B31" name="B31">
    <say>it looks like I got a message from Ms. Johnson and Dr. Arthur, how do I reply back to them?</say>
  </message>